# DANIEL GUTIERREZ DUQUE

# **CONTACT**

https://dgutierrezd.now.sh - Website

Manizales, Caldas, Colombia

+57 316 695 7790

danielgudu22@gmail.com

https://github.com/dgutierrezd

https://youtube.com/DanyCode

## SKILLS

React Native GraphQL

React JS Swift

Ruby on Rails NodeJS

Next.js SQL

SwiftUI AWS

## **LANGUAGES**

English (C1)

Spanish

#### **ABOUT ME**

I am a responsable person, helpful, creative, agile, open to acquire new knowledge and new skills, easily to work individually and at the group level; with a great experience working as web developer, using technologies like React and NextJS, being also a Fullstack developer working with backend technologies like NodeJS, Ruby on Rails and Spring Boot.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Mobile Developer, Blossom:

11/2022 - Current

- \* Lead mobile team and develop hardest features and modules.
- \* Deploy apps on Android and iOS stores (React - React Native - GraphQL - NodeJS)

Frontend Developer, Hylink:

08/2022 - 12/2022

Develop a web application using React JS and TypeScript (React - Node JS)

Mobile Developer, Revvy:

11/2021 - 07/2022

- \* Tech lead of mobile team
- \* Responsible for deploy and of the develop of mobile app
- \* Implement and design webhooks

(React Native - React - Next.js - PostgreSQL - AWS - NodeJS)

Web Developer, Webbost S.A.S:

12/2020 - 10/2021

- \* Create mobile app for scholar platform, being the unique developer.
- \* Create API with GraphQL
- \* Create Web platform for the teachers (React Node.js GraphQL AWS)

Fullstack Developer, Adisoft:

09/2018 - 06/2020

- \* Create multiple mobile apps using React Native
- \* Develop multiple SaaS to use on small business and buildings (React Spring Boot NodeJS Next.js)

Freelancer:

06/2017 - 09/2018

- \* Develop multiple mobile apps for medium business, using React Native, implementing animations.
- \* Responsible of all the flow of the app, since creation to deploy and maintenance.

(React Native- React - Next.js - NodeJS)

# **EDUCATION**

2017 - Today

Systems Engineer – Universidad Autónoma de Manizales

Centro Colombo Americano – Graduado en Noviembre de 2015, english level C1.

# **REFERENCIAS**

- Jorge Reinoso Software Developer +57 311 508 6385 - William Gustavo Giraldo Restrepo Senior Software Developer +57 313 700 4535